Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XCI is arranged in 34 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XCI. 1935 CONVENTION RESOLUTIONS
  - Sub-Series 461-0. 1935 Convention Resolutions. General
    - General, 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 461-1. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 1
    - Declaration of Brotherhood Policy, 1935-1937 (Box 601a, Folder 5)
    - Railway Pensions. 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 6)
    - Declaration of Brotherhood Policy. Railroad Wages, 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 7)
    - Railway Consolidations. 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 8)
    - Workmen's Compensation, 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 9)
    - Organization. Company Unions., 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 10)
    - Financial Reorganization. Railway Corporations., 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 11)
    - Waterways, 1935-1937 (Box 601a, Folder 12)
    - Government Ownership of Railroads, 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 13)
    - Social Security Act, 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 14)
    - Shorter Work Week, 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 15)
    - Wagner Labor Disputes Act, 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 16)
    - Wages. Outside Industries, 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 17)
    - National Industrial Recovery Act, 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 18)
    - Labor's Political Policy, 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 461-2. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 2
    - Employment of Oliver, E.L. as Research Director, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 461-3. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 3
    - Commending Governor Olsen of Minnesota for Actions in Teamsters Strike, 1935-1937 (Box 601a, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 461-4. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 4
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 461-6. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 6
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 461-8. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 8
    - General, 1935-1939 (Box 601a, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 461-11. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 11
    - Elimination of Non-Members, 1935-1947 (Box 601a, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 461-12. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 12
    - General, 1935-1937 (Box 601a, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 461-13. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 13
    - General, 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 461-14. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 14
    - General, 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 461-15. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 15
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 461-16. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 16
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 461-17. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 17
    - General, 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 461-18. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 18
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 461-20. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 20
    - General, 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 461-25. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 25
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 461-26. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 26
    - To Prevent Profiteering in War, 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 35)
    - To Prevent Profiteering in War. Text of H.R. 5529, An Act to Prevent Profiteering in Time of War, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 36)
      1935 May 1
  - Sub-Series 461-28. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 28
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 461-30. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 30
    - General, 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 461-34. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 34
    - General, 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 461-35. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 35
    - General, 1935-1937 (Box 601a, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 461-36. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 36
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 461-38. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 38
    - General, 1935-1937 (Box 601a, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 461-40. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 40
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 461-43. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 43
    - To Endorse Efforts to Prevent War, 1935-1941 (Box 601a, Folder 44)
    - To Endorse Efforts to Prevent War, 1935-1937 (Box 601a, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 461-48. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 48
    - General, 1935-1955 (Box 601a, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 461-50. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 50
    - General, 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 461-51. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 51
    - General, 1935-1938 (Box 601a, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 461-55. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 55
    - General, 1935-1937 (Box 601a, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 461-56. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 56
    - General, 1935-1937 (Box 601a, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 461-57. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 57
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 461-58. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 58
    - General, 1935-1936 (Box 601a, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 461-59. 1935 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 59
    - General, 1935 (Box 601a, Folder 53)